# Crying and laughing Every use the stars shine
♪ Feelings shake me, I don't even know
♪ Baby dance I'll break you in love
♪ Cry and laugh Every use the stars shine
If you want to shoot the same color, I just made a slight adjustment to the position of the camera.
Shall we take another one?
Yeah.
Is that okay?
Well, let me know if this is too wide or too narrow.
I just fixed it so you can all see.
Yeah, okay.
Let's see where you're standing.
And the last one?
Oh, yeah.
Let's see here.
The only one, she's the one, Emma's the one.
Emma.
Oh, it's a song.
It's a song.
So, it might be easier to recognize Emma if Yuna gets a little closer.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I feel like I'm in the middle of something. Sorry.
I'm alive.
This hourglass is ticking, too.
Oh, Primal.
Is this really sand? I see sugar or something.
Is there any left?
Baby, you must stay with us
My baby, you must
Thank you for watching.
I'm looking for it.
I've got your arm.
Thank you very much.
You're so cool.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you for your time.
This is the third of a trilogy, and all of them are totally different from each other,
The dance is also pop and catchy,
I was worried that I wouldn't be able to remember the dance moves because they were so detailed,
But now, after finishing the dance scene,
But now, after finishing the dance scene, I was relieved to see that everyone was able to dance smoothly,
I hope you will join me in dancing along with them,
We had a lot of fun filming the dance scene.
I'm going to cross.
Small vibrations approaching
Riding on the rhythm born of you and the prism
Ride the rhythm born with you and the prism.
I'm invincible, so now is the time to smile
Dream come true come
I see the ring, I chase it, I sneak in the stick
See, my heart starts to dance
Super pure
Dream come true come
My favorite style, classic, with you I'm invincible
Let's dance in the sky now
Tickle Tickle
Tickle Tickle Tickle
Mr. Datan
Thank you very much.
It's warm! Ya! It's warm! Warm! Oh, man!
Oh, man!
I did that in junior high.
No, not like this.
Oh, my God! I found this in the gym.
Middle school gym.
Oh, my God! What's this?
It's so hot!
There's so much stuff.
It's so big!
Hey, Mr. Dakan-tan.
Can I ask you to come inside?
It feels warm
Warm.
It's warm.
Absolutely useless.
Try this by warming your hands with it, okay?
It warms my hands.
My hands are in Hokkaido.
Hands are Hokkaido.
I didn't say that.
It's like grandma's house.
Grandma's house.
Was that it?
Not Tikori.
I don't know.
It was a stove back then.
The air feels like this.
I know what you mean.
It's like...
Warm.
It's getting cold.
Now was the time for three levers.
Peak Tech's lever.
Geraly nails.
Ribbons.
Look.
Ribbon.
Different.
No, it's not.
Are you trying to explain Japanese?
Turn around, good.
ontare
me
CAR
[the other
I'm a little nervous, but I'll take enquanto today.
Yes, so we are safe.
The music video shooting of Henklewink, we have finished.
We finished.
Today, it was cold,
How was it?
Yes, it was. The shooting location was really beautiful,
It was a beautiful place, a scripted ceremony hall, and so on.
The back of the dance scene was sparkling,
I thought it was amazing.
I also felt the harshness of music video shooting for the first time.
I see, it's never been like this before.
I had to endure the cold from early in the morning,
Or dancing outside.
Today's time was indoors,
I always shoot in a comfortable temperature,
Today was the first time I had to fight the cold.
But it's amazing what idol music videos can do,
It's often said that the colder it gets, the tighter the pores become and the cuter the idol looks.
So I'm really looking forward to seeing the finished product,
I really danced a lot,
I hope everyone will dance with me.
Will you still be watching it when it is completed?
Thank you very much for your time.
Wano sill Gung
We've finished filming!
We had a lot of the same scenes this time.
We were all next to each other a lot.
The three of us were together at the beginning with Yoon-o.
It was cold outside,
It was cold.
We danced a lot this time.
I want everyone to see that.
Look at that!
I endured the morning's bony trunks, so I was totally fine.
1,2,3,4
The shooting is over.
It was cold.
But I think this is the first music video in a while where I danced like crazy.
Yes, it was. It was outside in a very spacious and beautiful place,
The set was really beautiful.
It was so cute.
It was the first time for me to wear such a black-and-white costume,
It was fresh and fun.
I'm sure the music video will be absolutely adorable, so I'm looking forward to seeing it when it's finished.
I'm going to take a bath today to warm up.
Yes, I'm going to take a bath today to warm up. After that, I'm going to eat a nabe (hot pot).
It seems to be chicken nabe.
It's lukewarm.
I will eat.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I wanted to make it a little easier.
So the shooting is over.
What is that?
It's like a sparkle.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle, twinkle...
It's a twinkle.
That's right.
Twinkle twinkle twinkle.
Today, during the shooting, Yuno-san created a word for Hiko, what should I say? Was it a gift?
Twinkle twinkle twinkle in your eyes.
Well, you should say it to people when you think they are cute.
If you think it's cute, it would be really helpful if you could say "twinkle twinkle twinkle in your eyes" in comments on Instagram or in diaper pictures, while thinking about twinkle twinkle twinkle.
Mr. Nakayama actually made an awkward face when he was told.
I hope that everyone will use it.
How was it?
Well...
The music video shooting.
We worked harder than usual, from the morning until about 10:00 p.m., but this time we had a lot of breaks and had a lot of fun.
Shooting music videos is fun, but we were able to have more fun and spend more time warmly.
Really? I was listening to it a lot, but I was mostly listening to this one.
Because sometimes it's cold, and sometimes you have to sleep and go to bed.
But on the other hand, it's been a while since I've done a music video where I dance with gusto, so I think people will enjoy it again.
I don't know.
After you've seen it, I want you to see it again.
Many times.
Well, you are Tinkle Tinkle Tinkle, so goodbye.
Bye, bye, bye. Have a good day.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
It was colder than I thought. It was colder than I thought it would be.
This time, the music video mainly consists of dance scenes.
It's true. It's been a while.
You know.
It was cold.
It was cold,
It's kind of like the dance scene,
And the cuddling scenes, and the bread-drinking scenes,
I shot a lot of strange things,
I'm really looking forward to the completion of the film.
I wonder how they are connected.
The last scene, too,
It was very mysterious.
The two of us sitting on the bench looking off into the distance.
I wonder what it means.
But I really like this worldview,
Like this Shani Layer,
I was really excited by the feeling of the Western-style house.
Oh, wow.
It's true, this blonde hair color matches her hair color very well,
I was really excited to see the blonde hair, or rather, the hair color, which matches her current black costume.
It was an amazing beauty winner.
Thank you very much.
What's with the extensions?
That's right. I actually became a gal with extensions too.
Yay.
So please look forward to it.
Please take a look.
Bye bye.